# ZONGYU CARNES

#### CONTACT

+1 226 507 7957 bcarnes@uwaterloo.ca

#### **EDUCATION**

**GEOMATICS STUDENT** • SEPT 2022 - PRESENT

University of Waterloo – Waterloo, Ontario. Canada

Key Courses:
Functional Programming
Data Structures and Algorithms
Data Management
Cartography
Intro to GIS

### KEY SKILLS

- -Solid understanding of Linux and programming in Java as well as Spring and Vaadin. Fluent in C syntax. Capable of using IO and assertion testing.
- -Create high quality maps though QGIS and ArcGIS
- -Excellent communication skills gained through volunteering previous work experience.
- -Keen attention to detail from various roles requiring strong observation skills as well as persistent work ethic from being accustomed to near daily schedules.
- -Strong teamwork through working in team-oriented environments.

#### **SUMMARY**

A dedicated student with a strong desire for growth and to contribute, I offer a foundation of transferable skills and a commitment to excellence. While my professional experience may be limited, my academic journey and past experiences has instilled in me a robust work ethic, adaptability, and a hunger for new challenges.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

HEALTH AND SAFETY COORDINATOR • JUNE 2022 - AUG 2022

Brickworks Academy - Doon, Ontario

- -As a member of a four-person team, I successfully enforced covid guidelines while providing an encouraging, positive atmosphere in the summer camp for children.
- -Practiced effective communication ensuring clear and coordinated responses to when problems arise
- -Provided acted as backup for all roles in case of call-ins to ensure smooth operation

STUDENT VOLUNTEER • JUNE 2021 - AUG 2021

Lexington Rescue Mission - Lexington, KY, USA

- -Worked with an extremely diverse group of volunteers six days a week to bring help to the less fortunate and supported hundreds of clients requesting assistance.
- -Took on a variety of roles from the front desk to the back offices providing information and assistance to provide the best quality customer service

PIZZA MAKER • JUNE 2023 - PRESENT

The Civil - Waterloo, Ontario

- -In a tight-knit team of four, worked efficiently under pressure to serve our guests in a high-class restaurant.
- -Effectively organized the kitchen by keeping a comprehensive inventory ensuring smooth operations.

-Organization skills during student volunteering and other activities.

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

CPR-C and First Aid - 2022 Valid G2 - 2023 SLCP Level 3

## **LANGUAGES**

- -English (fluent)
- -Mandarin (speaking)